

Pushpa Veni Manti mantipv@gmail.com +1 385-384-6533 www.linkedin.com/in/mantipushpaveni

Mission Statement

Professional with 13 years of experience, strong financial modelling, and reporting skills, as well as SAP and payroll experience. As a graduate of Brigham Young University with an MBA in Finance, I am seeking employment in the financial planning and analysis.

Education

Brigham Young University, Marriott School of Business, Provo, Utah MBA Candidate, Emphasis in Finance & Analytics, April 2023

Brigham Young University, Provo, Utah

B. Com, Emphasis in Accounting, April 2009 Graduated Member of Deans List

Work Experience

Arrow Fish Consulting, Salt Lake City, UT 2022-2022

Business Valuation and Damage Experts

Finance Intern

Assisted The Valuation Team on Various Projects

- Developed an end-to-end SharePoint platform for the tracking and data retention of over 100+ compliance items for plants and incentive programs reducing data redundancy and centralizing data retention
- Analysed tax disclosure against two industry benchmarks and 50+ publicly held companies, summarizing my findings in a single page memo for the SVP of global tax
- Conducted in-depth financial and valuation analysis and modelling for 3 clients

Granules India Private Ltd, Hyderabad, India 2019-2021

Pharmaceutical Company

Finance And Operations Manager

Managed External Audit Relationship with Four Professional Clients

- Directed the migration of it control work from an outsourced model to in-house, leading to annual savings of approximately \$50,000
- Analysed it risk across applications, environments, databases, and processes, leading to the implementation of various controls to cover risk gaps
- Developed automation flows and a Microsoft power app to assist various departments in the tracking of month end procedures and the capturing of control documentation review reducing redundancy by 20%
- Maintaining the relationship with 10+ internal it contacts, resulting in the reduction of duplicative requests and processes by 50%

ADP India Private Ltd, Hyderabad, India 2013-2019

Financial services firm specializing in payroll services for Global Nike and IBM Senior Process Associate

Led a team of 2-3 Global Risk Staff

- Payroll administrator for Nike and ibm performed bi- weekly payroll for over 5000 employees
- Supervised daily fieldwork for teams of 12-15 employees, and performed detailed review of their work
- Assessed the design and operating effectiveness of corporate it and entity level controls for over eight corporation, with revenues more than \$5 billion each, to ensure compliance with Sox requirements
- Evaluated the design and operating effectiveness of 70+ application controls supporting the financial assurance teams audit opinion
- Managed business relationships with internal audit teams and key business / it corporate contracts

JK Bountiful Enterprises, Hyderabad, India 2012-2013

Architectural Firm that Specialized in Interior Design **Operations Analyst**

Recommend and update policies and procedures to improve performance

- Enhanced workflow and cross-departmental engagements
- Collaborated with the sales and engineering team to improve cost-effectiveness across all platforms
- Create monthly reports to management on key findings and assessments
- Evaluated the design and operating effectiveness of 70+ application controls supporting the financial assurance teams audit opinion
- Worked closely with executive management to achieve outcomes based on company goals
- Planned and reviewed compensation actions; enforcing policies and procedures
- Served as primary point of contact when there are customer issues related to equipment quality, customer service, or accidents and mishaps on-site

LSN Foundation, Hyderabad, India 2009-2012

NGO Firm that Specialized in Social Impact

Finance Manager

Cash Management, Paying Invoice, Monitoring Budgets, Developing Financial Forecasts and Creating Financial Reports

- Managed the engagement for 25-40 small/medium clients
- Demonstrated strategic planning experience at a management level

Additional

Brigham Young University, Marriott School of Business, Provo, Utah Cardon International Scholarship Recipient, 2021 to 2023

